We'll also cover Eric Adams and how they're trying to get him out of the race by bribing him. It's probably not a feeling he's unfamiliar with. We'll also talk about sanctions on Palestinians, nothing new there, but this time it's for having the temerity to oppose genocide. We'll get into the details. And this part, I don't know if you care about, John, but you fly a lot. Trump has decided to screw airline passengers, and I wonder if he'll pay a price for that in terms of populism, siding with one of the most hated industries in America, the airlines, against ordinary passengers. So, let's just get to it. What do you want to talk about first, John? I'd like to talk about Eric Adams first, if we could. Absolutely. Deep down, I still have a love for how the sausage is made at the State Department and in foreign policy. One thing about the Saudis, and this is why Saudi Arabia is being floated as a place for Eric Adams to end up, is that they have always insisted on not having a career diplomat as the U.S. ambassador. They demand a political appointee, which is exactly the opposite of most other countries. Why? Because they want to be able to pick up the phone, call the ambassador, and have the ambassador call the president, and the president takes the call. If you're a career diplomat, the president has never heard of you. You can't call the White House in the middle of the night and say, "The King of Saudi Arabia wants to talk to you." As crazy as this might sound, the Saudis would be very happy to have Eric Adams as the U.S. ambassador. That's not to say that 51 U.S. senators will agree to have Eric Adams as the U.S. ambassador. Although, if he were to drop out of the race and the Republicans endorse Cuomo, he'll still lose. We need to break this down for people who are not watching the details of the New York City mayoral race, which is super important, even if you don't live in or care about New York, just because it's the epic showdown inside the Democratic Party between the progressive left base of the party and the corporatist centrists who run the DNC. In the primary, Mamdani, the democratic socialist, basically a Bernie acolyte, managed to defeat a crowded field and is now the Democratic nominee in the general election. Current polls, I just checked the RealClearPolitics averages, show Zohran Mamdani at 38.2%. In a distant second is Andrew Cuomo, the former New York governor, running as a third-party candidate on the Fight Anti-Semitism line. Subtle. Cygni Wilkinson, the editorial cartoonist for the Philadelphia Inquirer, is delightful, and she says in moments like that, which you just reminded me of. Curtis Sliwa, the founder of the Guardian Angels and the perennial Republican nominee, is at 16.6%. Basically, as popular as lint is the sitting incumbent mayor, Eric Adams, who is currently at 10.6%. So, the powers that be are looking at one outlying poll that seems to indicate that if you could get Adams and hopefully Sliwa to drop out, but certainly Adams, you might actually be able to beat Mamdani with Cuomo. The billionaire class, real estate interests, Wall Street, all those people—that's their plot here, right? They're trying to clear the field for Cuomo. Oddly, the New York Post, the Murdoch organ here in New York, is still trying to push for Adams. Honestly, Clovis, my cat, has a far better chance of being mayor than Adams. Seriously, there's no way. He's at 10.6% in the race, and he's the incumbent. Mamdani is increasing in the polls. Adams has faced many very credible corruption charges. I can't say that he's corrupt, but in my opinion, he is corrupt and takes bribes. I think that's the opinion of most New Yorkers, too. So, the idea is to get rid of Adams. If Adams drops out and endorses Cuomo, they'll work on Sliwa. Sliwa says there's absolutely nothing that can convince him to drop out. He said he'd have to be run over by a car to drop out of the race. I kind of believe Curtis. It just seems very desperate, right? Steve Witkoff, the Trump envoy to various global hotspots, including Russia and Ukraine, is floating this. We don't know how far up the food chain this has gone. We don't know if the Donald is on board with this, or if he's just reading about it. How likely is this? You know what? I think it's actually likely because Donald Trump isn't stupid. We like to criticize Donald Trump, sure, but he's not stupid, and his political instincts are obvious. If he were a stupid man, he'd be in jail right now. He wouldn't be the first person elected president without military or political experience. He's not stupid. He knows that Eric Adams isn't going to win this race. There's a better chance that Trump can have some serious input if he gets Adams out. So, what do you do? You offer him the ambassadorship to Saudi Arabia. Why not? That will make him happy, and the Saudis want a political appointee anyway. Then, he at least throws a little wrench into the Mamdani campaign, even if Trump has already concluded that Mamdani is going to win. Getting Eric Adams out of the race at least forces Mamdani to spend some money and allows people to coalesce around the candidate Trump wants, which is neither Curtis Sliwa nor Andrew Cuomo. It just makes it a little tougher for Mamdani. Mamdani has already got the maximum number of campaign contributions he's allowed to accept. People are throwing so much money at him. It's hard to see how he loses at this stage, and he's increasing in the polls. The more people pay attention to him, the more they like him in New York. I think all this establishment stuff is just counterproductive. It's just blowback, right? It's super interesting to see how this is all playing out. I guess Eric Adams gets a soft landing. How is that post, though? We talked yesterday about the ambassadorial position in Athens, which all humans can agree is a nice job. How is Riyadh? You and I have similar views on what it's like to live in Saudi Arabia. My personal view is that Saudi Arabia is the biggest open-air prison in the world, but that's just me. When I was serving in Saudi Arabia, I served under two ambassadors. One was Chas Freeman, the legendary Chas Freeman, who, God bless him, is still alive. He has some health problems, but he is one of the leading voices out there in support of the Palestinian people. He went on to be the Assistant Secretary of Defense and was supposed to be chairman of the National Intelligence Council, but the Obama people killed the nomination because he's pro-Palestinian. The second ambassador I served under had been the governor of Mississippi and then Bill Clinton's Secretary of the Navy. Nice guy, sweet guy, completely out of his element. He just did what he was told to do. Whoever was the National Security Advisor, Sandy Berger for most of that period, just told him what to do, and he did it. That's what the Saudis wanted. If you're the ambassador, life is good because you're meeting with the king, the crown prince, and the minister of foreign affairs. You have the biggest parties in the country and the biggest mansion in the diplomatic quarter. Life's going to be good. As soon as you step out of that house, life’s not so good because Saudi Arabia is a terrible, terrible place to be. I’d rather be almost anywhere else than Saudi Arabia. The ambassador lives in a compound, can have alcohol, has high walls, and can pretty much do whatever they want. They’re living in their own private Idaho, right? Like a wild potato. Don’t go on the patio. But that’s basically it. You’re in your Wally World. It’s awful. Every once in a while, you get in the car and go to Dhahran to meet the people at the consulate there. Then you take a quick flight to Jeddah. The Saudi government moves to Jeddah in May, June, July, and August because Riyadh is too hot—120, 125 degrees. They go to Jeddah because it’s on the water, and you get a little breeze. It’s still 120 degrees, but it’s all relative, I suppose. The reason they want you in the first place is that they want someone whose phone calls the president will take. That’s the bottom line. Adam wants to know, is it true that if you want to work in Saudi Arabia, you’re appointed a handler by the government, your passport is taken away, and you can only leave with their permission? Yes, that is true. It’s a serious human rights problem. You have to be sponsored. On your visa application, you must state who your sponsor is. A Saudi must be the majority shareholder of whatever company you’re working for. You can’t just go to Saudi Arabia and say, “I’m going to open an LLC and make widgets.” No, you own 49%, and some random Saudi owns 51%. The Saudi holds your passport, and if they don’t like you or you have a falling out over money, you’re essentially under house arrest because you can’t go anywhere. That’s how they keep, especially South Asian women, as sex slaves. They hire them as domestics, nannies, or English teachers, and when they arrive, the sponsor takes their passport and says, “Now take your clothes off, and you’re going to live in the cupboard under the stairs.” Lovely. Best system. I hated it there. Good thing we’re so close to them. Marble wants to know, and thanks for the generous donation—thanks also to Houdini and everyone else—your thoughts on Nigel Farage. As recently as five years ago, Nigel Farage was a joke, a kind of neo-Nazi fascist weirdo from the British right wing. Over the last five years, with the electoral humiliation that the Conservative Party underwent, Farage has emerged as a real voice on the right. He’s no less fascistic than he was five years ago, but he’s been accepted by the mainstream as a legitimate right-wing voice. When I was last in London in March, there was an article in The Times of London, a conservative paper owned by Rupert Murdoch, saying that Nigel Farage would likely be the next leader of the Conservative Party. If that happens, I could see the end of the Conservative Party as a viable political force. Conservatives who aren’t that conservative, called “wets,” would move to the Liberal Party, which is not liberal but actually quite conservative, especially on foreign policy. The Nigel Farage conservatives would just be a rump party. Farage is a very interesting character because he reminds me of what I’ve read happened in the UK in conservative politics in the run-up to the Second World War. There were a lot of Brits who thought Hitler was A-OK, and it took years for them to choose sides, like the Oswald Mosley types. The British Fascist Party was a real thing, and there were members of the royal family who were part of it. Thank you so much to Peter for becoming a monthly supporter. Let’s talk about the politics here. I’ve got to think that the reason Trump’s not all in on this plan is that he knows it probably won’t work. He doesn’t want to get behind a plan that’s likely to fail, and then he’ll be made fun of, which he hates. There are a lot of moving parts here. In the end, Donald Trump does things that benefit Donald Trump. How does this benefit him? It doesn’t really. I think the Republican Party is planning to go after Mamdani and turn him into their punching bag for the next four years. I wouldn’t be so sure it’s going to work. He seems like a really smart young man who’s surrounding himself with older, seasoned New Yorkers who will guide him at Gracie Mansion and City Hall. They’ll tell him how things work. I don’t think he’s going to go in there like a bull in a china shop. He’s been running a great campaign. When Mamdani came out ahead, many in the center and on the right said it was a fluke, temporary, and that everyone would coalesce around Cuomo, and the DNC would live happily ever after. That’s not happening. His political godfather happens to be Jewish, so when people say, “Mamdani’s going to open ovens for the Jews,” no, he’s not. New York voters, many of whom are Jewish, are voting for him, and they know what he’s about. Nixon Barley says all of Trump’s advisors are young guys. I’ve got to tell you, though, he had that guy—his name escapes me—who ran against him in the primary and then endorsed him. They kind of co-endorsed each other in the primary, and he’s older than we are. He’s holding strong. Before we move on, we’ve got a good question from Road Beef. If we mentioned Farage, I must also ask Ted and John for their opinion on Boris Johnson—two peas in a pod. Nobody in the UK was more shocked when Boris Johnson became prime minister than Boris Johnson himself. He was a provocateur journalist who made a career by pissing people off on purpose. He was one of those original “I have an opinion” right-wing journalists, the “what are you going to do about it?” kind of people. He got into politics just to troll people, and one crazy thing led to another, and he found himself prime minister. Every time I go to the UK, I visit my host family, who sponsored me when I was 19. They’re absolutely wonderful people. My host father was a member of parliament in the 1980s for the Liberal Party. He’s in his late eighties now but still 100% sharp and follows every detail of politics. He said at the time that Johnson never wanted to be prime minister. It was all about lighting a fire under people and then writing a book about it later to promote himself on TV. He didn’t think he’d actually become prime minister. It was like Trump—there are a lot of dogs catching cars nowadays. For Trump, it was about enhancing the brand. He didn’t think he was going to win. So, you find yourself prime minister of the UK, yelling about Brexit for months, and you’ve got to Brexit. Two great lines from the scroll. Houdini says, “Mamdani, regardless of what he says during the campaign, if he wins, he’ll get the talk and fall in line, just like AOC did.” James Gernales says, “Youth and cunning will always be outdone by age and treachery.” Amen. That’s a tattoo-worthy line. It’s an ugly world we live in. Ross Houston wants to know how valuable access to a high-level member of the UAE’s economy cabinet would be to the CIA. Not very valuable. The CIA doesn’t really spy on the UAE because they give us everything we want. We don’t care about their economy. What we care about most is their commitment to the alliance with the United States against Iran and the Houthis. The Brits make the UAE economy run—they’re the bankers and advisors managing the National Wealth Fund. Speaking of the talk, if young bloods like Mamdani get the talk from old-school dudes who tell them what’s what, I think Trump has a boss too—the corporations. Trump obviously got a call from the airline CEOs, saying, “Don’t you dare go ahead with this last-second Biden-Buttigieg plan that would have required airlines to pay passengers when delays are their fault, not due to weather.” Remember when Southwest failed to upgrade their computer systems, and people got delayed? If you fly, you know how aggravating this is. It happened to my son recently. He’s changing planes, the airline messed up, he misses his connection, and he’s stuck in a strange city. They’re like, “You can sleep in the airport overnight, or you can shell out for a hotel on your own dime and pay for extra meals.” In Europe, they have a system—imperfect, but if the airline messes up, you can put in a claim, and they have to compensate you. Buttigieg and outgoing Biden pushed this through, like too many good things they came up with, in a cowardly way on their way out the door. It never went into effect, and now Trump is quietly getting rid of it on a Friday. Airlines are scum. They make billions in profits, squeezing us in. It’s unsafe to fly. I’m 6’2” and jammed in the seats, but that’s not my main concern. Deep vein thrombosis I can live and die with, but if you ever had to evacuate a plane, which I’ve had to do, you can’t because the aisles are too narrow. It’s a safety issue. This is such a corporatist, Reagan-type move. By itself, it’s not enough to destroy Trump’s coalition, but if there were more of this, do you think Trump would lose populist conservatives like producer Robbie, who voted for him, or would they just not be aware of it? Unfortunately, I think it’s the latter. Most people aren’t paying attention. Americans have accepted being treated like cattle. I was in Spain earlier this year and had to fly from Madrid to Dublin, then Dublin to Washington. There was a mechanical problem in Madrid. They fixed the plane, but I missed my connection in Dublin. Since it wasn’t my fault, I went to the information desk and said I was on the flight from Madrid. They said, “We’ve been waiting for you, Mr. Kiriakou. Unfortunately, there’s no flight to Washington until tomorrow. We’ve booked you in a four-star hotel with a buffet breakfast that could feed an army, and we’re refunding $600 of your $1,200 ticket.” I went to the hotel, they had a shuttle bus, expedited check-in, a gorgeous hotel in the center of Dublin, a gigantic buffet. I did some sightseeing, flew to Washington the next morning, and six weeks later, I got $600 transferred into my checking account. Why don’t we do that? We should. Even with weather delays, there should be some compensation. Maybe airlines could charge an extra fee for a compensation fund. It’s not their fault if there’s a storm, but people need to stay at a hotel. DeWolfson, thank you so much for becoming a monthly supporter. This airline news stuck in my craw, and I noticed it was a Friday news dump when people are outside enjoying the weekend. They know this isn’t popular. I still maintain Pete Buttigieg is the front-runner for the Democratic nomination in 2028, not Gavin Newsom. If I’m Buttigieg, I’m doing a little dance because I can say, “I promoted this, and Trump killed it. I’m on your side. Trump is on the airlines’ and corporations’ side.” Here’s an ad: Thanks, everyone, for listening. If you haven’t already, make sure you download the Rumble app. It’s free, simple to use, and the best way to stay connected to the content you want. Search for our channel and hit follow so you’ll get a notification every time we go live. No missed shows, no extra steps. Grab it using the link in the description or the pinned live chat, download it to your phone, and you’re ready to go. If you prefer watching on the big screen, Rumble is available on all major streaming devices and smart TVs. Just search for Rumble, follow the channel, and be part of the action. Please watch us on Rumble because that’s where we make the financial action. Thanks to our viewers and producer Robbie, we were on Rumble’s front page the other day, boosting our viewership by about 9 or 10%. It’s insanely appreciated. Peter says every airport should have Dante’s Divine Comedy inscribed: “Abandon all hope, ye who enter here.” It’s a bleak feeling walking into an airport. Even with TSA PreCheck, it’s an undignified experience. They’re like, “We found your applesauce, criminal.” I’d get rid of TSA entirely and go back to the old days when you could walk your loved ones to the gate. My son thought I was kidding when I told him that. When I was a boy visiting relatives in Washington, D.C., my dad took me to National Airport. There was an observation deck on the roof of the terminal where you could watch planes take off and land. It was awesome for a kid. Now kids are like, “That never happened.” In the early ’90s, my sister-in-law couldn’t use the return on her round-trip ticket. I used it, and they didn’t even check my ID. Her name was Alice, and the guy gave me a funny look. I said, “Like Alice Cooper,” and he let me on. I bought my parents tickets on Bahamas Express from Kennedy to the Bahamas for their anniversary—$99 for a day trip. They couldn’t use them because my dad had already booked a trip to Greece. I was stuck with non-refundable tickets, so I took my brother. My mom’s name is Stella. The guy looked at the ticket, then at me, and said, “Buddy, $50 name change fee next time.” I got on, and we had a great day in the Bahamas. Back then, TSA didn’t exist, and box cutters were legal to bring on planes. What do you make of the fact that you have to go through an anal probe to get on a plane, but trains and buses have no security? I’m amazed there aren’t more terrorist attacks. Has there ever been a terrorist attack against a train in the U.S.? The last one I can think of was the South Moluccas terrorists in Holland in the 1970s who hijacked a train. Carlos the Jackal killed French policemen on a train in the ’70s. You and I travel by train frequently on the East Coast—it’s the only way to get between Boston and Washington. They don’t even look at your ticket until the train’s moving. You don’t need ID; you just get on. It’s a beautiful thing. Buses like Greyhound and Bolt don’t care either. Houdini’s right—there was that attack thwarted by U.S. airmen on the TGV, a Greek-American hero. MW Knox wants to know if we prefer the scanner or the pat-down. I’ll take the scanner. I hate strangers touching me like that. At the airport now, they say, “Stand over here, and we’ll take your photo.” It’s optional, but they don’t tell you that. You have to say, “I decline,” and they don’t like it. It delays you a couple of minutes, but you can decline. A friend at The New York Times, Jewish with dual Israeli citizenship, was flying out of Tel Aviv after working on a kibbutz. They decided to do a body cavity search. I was like, “Including your anus?” He said, “Yeah.” I asked what he did, and he said he didn’t want to miss his flight. I’d have called the U.S. embassy and missed my flight for a week. I got strip-searched in Iceland down to my underwear and was raging mad but didn’t say a word to avoid giving them satisfaction. If I’d refused, they probably would’ve told me to leave the airport, and there’s no other way out of Iceland. OMG, Jen wants you to finish your train story. I don’t remember what I was saying about the train. If you think of it, Jen, let me know, and I’ll finish it. We did Eric Adams, so we should talk about the War Department. It was the Department of War until 1947 when President Truman changed it because it sounded warmongering. We’d just won World War II, and everyone loved us, so why change it? He didn’t want the U.S. to be seen as an aggressor or imperialist. We’re all relatively intelligent people and can tell the difference between defense and offense. We’ve been an offensive military country since achieving superpower status after World War II, invading and overthrowing governments all over the globe. It is a Department of War, so I have no problem with this change. Trump signed an executive order today mandating the change, but a president can’t change a federal department’s name—it requires an act of Congress. Do you think Democrats will go along with it? It’s a simple majority vote, but you need 60 in the Senate to break cloture. There are more important things to worry about, so I don’t think Democrats will care, though they may oppose it to make life harder for Trump. Pacifists have been saying for years it should be called the War Department, so I’m wondering what they’ll say. Trump’s statement yesterday was hilariously insipid: “Defense sounds too defensive. We also have to be offensive.” Don’t worry, Donald, you’re always offensive. It’s dumb, but I’m fine with it. I wonder if it’ll backfire and make war appropriations harder to rubber-stamp in the future. We have an important question from My Good Sir with a $10 donation. Can you cover the breaking story about U.S. Marines going into North Korea and killing civilians? It’s a huge story. The New York Times broke it, reporting that in 2018, when relations with North Korea were thawing, and Trump hoped for a rapprochement, they wanted to learn more about Kim’s thinking. They had a device to eavesdrop on his communications, but it had to be planted on North Korean soil. SEAL Team 6 was assigned the task. They planned and practiced, but the weather was off, the landing didn’t go right, and the water was super cold. A North Korean boat arrived, and nobody spoke Korean. They thought something was going on, aborted the operation, shot the people on board—who turned out to be fishermen—killed everyone, and took off without planting the device. The New York Times reported that SEAL Team 6 and similar groups often have botched operations, bragging about successes but not failures. Trump had to sign off because it was so risky—they could’ve been captured or killed, causing a massive international incident. There was a serious violation of protocol because the White House didn’t inform the Gang of Four (the chairman and vice chairman of the Senate and House Intelligence Committees) or the full committees before or after the operation. Heads should’ve rolled, but nothing happened. Trump’s response was, “I don’t know anything about it. I’m hearing it now for the first time.” That’s a lie. He had to sign a finding authorizing it. That’s how covert operations work. Hello at Gossam asks about Afia Siddiqui. I had her attorney, Clive Stafford Smith, over for coffee today, and we recorded an episode of my Deep Focus podcast. Afia Siddiqui was a Pakistani-American neurosurgeon with a Ph.D. from Brandeis and a bachelor’s from MIT, absolutely brilliant. Her sister is also a Ph.D. neurologist or neurosurgeon. Afia self-radicalized around 9/11 and went back to Pakistan, volunteering to join Al Qaeda. We captured Khalid Sheikh Mohammed in August 2002, and he ratted her out. We found her in Karachi, the Pakistanis grabbed her, gave her to us, and we took her to Afghanistan and locked her up. She had three young children—a boy, a girl, and an infant. She was turned over from the Pakistanis to the Afghans, then to the Americans. The FBI began interrogating her. The official story is that she was in a tent waiting to be interrogated. An FBI agent leaned his M4 against the tent, she grabbed it, tried to shoot him, the gun jammed, and another agent shot her twice in the stomach. She survived. She was charged with attempted murder, found guilty, and given 86 years in prison—the longest sentence in U.S. history for attempted murder where no weapon was discharged. During the trial, they showed two bullet holes in the tent’s canvas, claiming she fired shots. Another photograph surfaced showing the bullet holes were there weeks before she was caught. She didn’t fire any shots. The CIA kidnapped her three children and turned them over to Christian missionaries in Kabul. The eldest son and daughter were adopted by missionary families who changed their names. No one knows what happened to the baby. When the war ended, Hamid Karzai, Afghanistan’s president, was under house arrest. Clive Stafford Smith befriended the Taliban government, told them about Afia, a hero in Pakistan and Afghanistan, and got to Karzai. Karzai admitted they turned the kids over to the CIA, who farmed them out for adoption. Clive found the two older children, now adults, and reunited them with Afia’s sister in Pakistan. The baby would be 18 now. The only news was that the baby was dropped on his head and killed, which Clive thinks is [ __ ]. He got Afia’s sister to give a DNA sample, registered it with 23andMe, GEDmatch, and Ancestry.com, and used AI to age the baby’s picture to what he’d look like at 18. He’s suing the CIA and FBI, knowing it’ll go nowhere, hoping to garner attention so an 18-year-old might take a DNA test. Afia is at FMC Carswell, a maximum-security medical prison, in solitary confinement since 2008. She’s lost her mind, but prison doctors claim she’s faking it. On Thanksgiving, she was given a plate with turkey, potatoes, stuffing, corn, and pumpkin pie, but didn’t eat, saying she was saving it for her son because he must be hungry. They wrote it up as faking PTSD. Clive Stafford Smith, a member of the Order of the British Empire for his human rights work, has never charged a client and lives on donations. He’s represented 66 Guantanamo detainees and got them all released. Write to him at clivestaffordsmith2020@gmail.com, and he’ll deliver letters to Afia. Her only hope is Trump commuting her sentence to let her go home to Pakistan, which isn’t likely. Her side of the story is believable. She was sitting in a chair in the tent when the FBI arrived. Hearing them speak English, she thought the Americans would save her from the Pakistanis and Afghans. She took off her veil, looked through the tent slit, a soldier said she was trying to escape, and he shot her twice in the stomach. Breaking news: A federal judge blocked Kristi Noem and the Trump administration from removing Biden-era protections for Venezuelans and Haitians they’re trying to deport. U.S. District Judge Edward Chen said Noem illegally stripped that status in a truncated timeline that didn’t follow the law. Another court defeat for Trump, but they likely saw it coming. Here’s another ad: A quick pause to tell you about Pickaxe, the creator- and user-first platform built for people, not algorithms. You know what Big Tech is up to—data mining, bot-driven feeds, black-box AI deciding who sees your work. Pickaxe offers an algorithm-free chronological feed with native Rumble playback, auto-publishing of live streams, free blue check verification, and full monetization control. Your voice, your rules. The web version is live, and iOS and Android apps drop next month. Your Rumble videos play seamlessly in your Pickaxe feed—no embeds, no workarounds. In beta, creators can connect their Rumble channel to Pickaxe to auto-post live streams and videos. You can write full articles on Pickaxe, and later this year, blast them as email newsletters with one click and build your email list. Monetize through paywalls, revenue sharing, or affiliate ads with auto-inserted promo codes and tracking links. Pickaxe gives you a free blue check so everyone knows it’s you. It’s building tech that builds up humanity—algorithm-free, noise-free, human-first. Head to pickaxe.com, sign up, and take your platform to the next level. Real voices deserve a real home. The Trump administration’s strategy is to do what they want and let people sue. They lose 50-70% of the time but do what they want in the interim and win a few. They expect to lose and don’t care. The Trump administration just imposed sanctions against three Palestinian groups—the Palestinian Center for Human Rights, Al-Haq, and Al Mezan—for asking the International Criminal Court to investigate alleged Israeli war crimes in Gaza without Israel’s consent. These are Marco Rubio’s sanctions. His complaint was that they didn’t get Israel’s permission. Next time I’m pulled over for speeding, I’ll file a complaint against the officer for not getting my consent to use the radar gun. If you watch YouTube, you know to scream, “I do not consent!” at the window—it always works. The Israelis have lost their minds. When will we call them on their [ __ ]? I’m optimistic it’s inevitable, maybe under Trump or someone like him, someone usually in their pocket who says, “Enough.” It might be out of left field, like when France recognized Palestine, and the dam bursts. JD Vance is a good guess. He’ll be anything you want—anti-Trump Republican, pro-Trump Republican, whatever. That’s it for an awesome week. If you’re not on Rumble Premium, consider it to check out my interviews with John and producer Robbie. Their stories are amazing. We’ve dropped three hour-long episodes about John’s life, with two or three more coming. It’s a privilege to do them. I sent the links to friends, and they loved them. Check out johnkiriakou.com, which we’ll beef up soon. I’m appearing on the Joe Rogan podcast on October 9th, with his 18.9 million subscribers, which might drive traffic to the site. I’ll talk about The DeProgram and Deep Focus and restart my speaking tour in December. Visit rall.com for my cartoons, columns, and my latest book, What’s Left, a prescription for what the real left, not the Democratic Party, should demand domestically and in foreign policy. Get it at rall.com, Amazon, or your local bookstore. Thank you for tuning in—it’s super appreciated. Thanks to producer Robbie West and Putin Bot Gaming. Check out his gaming channel on YouTube and Rumble. He’s part of Rumble’s content creator program, so pop over, say howdy, or call him names—it helps his chat metrics. He’s keeping this going, so throw some watch hours his way. Have a great weekend, everyone. We’re back Monday through Friday, 5 p.m. Eastern. Like, follow, and share the show on Rumble. Bye. text